The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Try to catch me !
Here, hurry up !
Don’t worry, Second Brother.
One day, Tie Zhu will return too.
We’ll throw him an even grander welcome feast.
That kid is Wang Hao, right ?
Long time no see !
Wang Hao
Xuan Dao Sect disciple
4th layer of Qi Condensation
Wang Hao !
It’s only been a few years since you left for training.
You’ve changed so much !
I just trained my alchemy.
If you want to talk about big changes,
Tie Zhu’s cultivation has long surpassed both of ours.
He isn't very talented
Wang Zhuo
Xuan Dao Sect disciple
11th layer of Qi Condensation
so even if he works hard he won't get very far.
Alright, let’s not talk about him.
Today, we drink until we drop !
Okay.
Why is the weather changing ?
What’s happening ?
Is this a mirror ?
Is that an Immortal ?
It really is an Immortal !
I guess he is.
Paying respects to Seniors !
I am Wang Zhuo of the Xuan Dao Sect.
I am Wang Hao.
Immortals ! They really are Immortals !
We are holding a feast today at the Wang Family.
May I ask why Seniors
came here ?
This old man is looking for someone !
So the Corpse Sect sent disciples into Jue Ming Valley
and allowed their Corpse Puppets to devour them
making them Late stage Foundation Establishment.
This does indeed increase their chances of keeping the token.
Late stage Foundation Establishment ?
I wonder what kind of artifacts you have
since you managed to escape.
Please Immortal, bless us !
Immortal, bless us !
What’s happening ?
What is this ?
Something’s wrong...
Your close relatives
are connected by blood.
Fellow cultivator Teng...
It’s not too late to stop now.
Li’er is already dead.
It's too late to back down !
Found him !
The Wang Family Village ?
Father ! Mother !
Tie Zhu ?
Why is Tie Zhu here ?
It’s Tie Zhu...
Tie Zhu !
Wang Lin...
You’re Teng Huayuan !?
What do you want !?
What do I want ?
Blood for blood.
I will wipe out your Wang Family to avenge my grandson Teng Li !
What is this ?
Don’t touch it !
Stop !
Immortal !
How has our Wang Family offended you ?
Why is this happening ?
Why ?
I will not spare a single soul today !
I’m the one who killed him !
I’m the one who stole his cultivation !
I’m in Jue Ming Valley right now.
Now come and kill me !
Teng Huayuan !
If you dare, come and kill me !
Kill you ?
Let's not rush this.
Don’t act rashly, he’s a Nascent Soul old monster.
Stop !
Stop now !
They have nothing to do with this,
I’m the one you want !
Teng Huayuan !
Got you !
Tie Zhu !
If you dare, come and kill me !
You have nowhere left to run...
Hand over your body now !
Come to Jue Ming Valley and kill me,
Teng Huayuan !
Wang Lin dared to kill my grandson
so I'll exterminate his entire family !
Father !
Mother !
The Ji Realm ?
Tie Zhu...
There is something wrong with this kid.
Fellow cultivator Teng,
leave this one to me.
I have a use for him.
Why are you doing this ? Why !?
We must survive.
Only by living can we take our revenge !
You won’t interfere with these two, will you ?
Why are you asking when you know the answer ?
If you kill them in front of me,
I won’t stop you.
But if Piao Nanzi asks me,
I’ll naturally tell him the truth.
Tie Zhu...
Tie Zhu ?
This bead contains my Divine Sense.
If you’re ever in danger,
you just need to crush it
and I'll come immediately.
Father...
Crush the bead I gave you, hurry up !
Hurry up !
My son,
no matter what you have done,
you must take care of yourself.
Only then will we be at peace.
No... No !
Father ! Mother !
Li’er, are you watching this ?
I'm just getting started !
Noooo !!!
My son, it doesn't matter if you are not chosen.
You can always come back,
we will always be there for you.
Tie Zhu...
you really look like an Immortal now.
I have never been so proud in my life.
Wang Lin,
I will wait for you
outside the valley in 3 months.
If you don’t show up,
I will make sure that
your parents' souls never reincarnate !
The Corpse Sect’s Late stage Foundation Establishment Corpse Puppets
were all killed in one strike...
Retreat !
Who’s there ? Don’t interfere !
Die !
Father, Mother, I will definitely succeed
in next year's imperial exams.
Silly boy, don’t push yourself so hard.
Father...
Mother...
Do you understand now ?
If my cultivation was higher,
then even if I slaughtered everyone in Teng Family City,
Teng Huayuan wouldn’t dare to say a word.
Let alone target my parents.
You just broke through a bottleneck by accident
unlocking the Ji Realm.
The Ji Realm ?
Ji means extreme.
The Ji Realm is the strongest type of cultivation.
The Ji Realm will overpower your peers of the same level.
But it also limits the user.
There has never been
a Ji Realm user who has broken through
above the level of Nascent Soul.
You won't be able to reach higher levels.
A Soul Flag is an artifact made by Nascent Soul cultivators.
It can store souls.
As long as their souls remain,
I will revive them
once I get back my cultivation.
Really !?
Yes.
When you inevitably fight Teng Huayuan,
just steal the Soul Flag.
I don’t have much energy left.
Maybe 3 teleportations maximum.
The Foreign Battlefield will open in 3 months.
After you steal the Soul Flag,
you should try to go there.
Only Foundation Establishment cultivators can enter it.
If we go there, I will have time to recover.
You're right Senior,
I don't have enough time.
3 months later
It’s you...
What do you want ?
Hand over all your tokens
or else...
die !
The Piao Miao Sect forfeits.
When the valley opens,
we’ll leave immediately.
Who has the last token ?
Liu Mei has it.
Liu Mei used me to distract the other sects
and ensure the Xuan Dao Sect keeps the last token.
If you spare me,
I’ll take you to Liu Mei !
I just want your token, not your lives.
Foundation Establishment ?
Thank you for sparing me.
The Foreign Battlefield cleanup
is a crucial trial of the cultivation world.
All of the Sect Ancestors are outside the valley,
including Teng Huayuan.
This concentrated Ji Realm cold energy is my best bet.
There are 7 tokens
so you should destroy 6
just to be absolutely sure.
Now, I just have one last thing to do.
Wang Lin, you have nowhere left to run !
This will be fun to watch...
Teng Huayuan !
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?